Sarthak

3D Artist, Full Stack Developer

Contact

Address

Chandigarh, India, 160019

Phone

9056317518

E-mail

sarthaksnh5@gmail.com

Github

github.com/sarthaksnh5

Skills

Technical Skills

Programming Language: Python, JavaScript, C

Tools: Blender, Fusion 360

Framework: Django, React

Native, Selenium

Database: MySQL,

Personal skills

Good interpersonal and communication skills.

Excellent problem solving and analytical skills.

Ability to work independently with Leadership skills.

A Man with the tech and speech, having the knowledge of tech and ability of express the use and put his words on the table.

Worked as freelancer for more than 18 projects in website development as well as 3D Artist in Fusion 360 and Blender

Work History

2020-06 -2022-04

Intern at IDEX (Innovation for Defence Excellence)

- Worked as a Team Lead to develop the portal for defence innovation idea entries.
- Automated the documentation of the entries of the candidate
- Automatic generation of agreement between the organization and candidate depending upon the data fill.

2020-06 -2022-04

Intern at Niti Aayog

- Worked on development of frontend and backend of the ATL Tinkerpreneur Website which is 9-week long program
- Designed a software to automate the deployment and addition of schools(data) on the online ATL dashboard
- Development of prototype of an AI-Chatbot for automated query resolution

Education

2018-06 -2022-05 Bachelor of Technology: Computer Science

Chandigarh College of Engineering and Technology

